Guide to Central Washington University Business and Financial Affairs 2019
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
  - Department of Auditing and Control, 1997- (Box-folder 54-7)
  - Audit Exercise, 1998- (Box-folder 54-8)
  - Audit, 1999- (Box-folder 54-9)
  - Audit, 2000- (Box-folder 54-10)
  - Comments on Reorganization, 2000- (Box-folder 54-11)
  - Audit, 2001- (Box-folder 54-12)
  - Vice President, Rich Corona, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 54-13)
  - Wage Garnishments, Education Loan fund, Cease and Desist, 1953-1995 (Box-folder 55-1)
  - China Program, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 55-2)
  - Use of Service and Activities Fees, 1991- (Box-folder 55-3)
  - Facilities Management, Audit, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 55-4)
  - Financial Services, Audit Recommendations, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 55-5)
  - Entrance Conference Audit of Auxiliaries, 2000- (Box-folder 55-6)
  - interagency Agreement WA State Auditor, 2000- (Box-folder 55-7)
  - Audit Recommendations, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 55-8)
  - Audit Management Letter, Items, 2001- (Box-folder 55-9)
  - Audit Entrance Conference, 2002- (Box-folder 55-10)
  - State Audit Reports, 2002- (Box-folder 55-11)
  - J. Antonich File, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 55-12)
  - State Audit Reports, 2003- (Box-folder 55-13)
  - Unemployment Information, 2009- (Box-folder 55-14)
  - Western Association of Colleges and University Business Office, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 55-15)
  - U.S. Bank, Agreement, 2010- (Box-folder 55-16)
  - General Operating Fund, Spending Projection, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 55-17)
  - Real Estate Acquisitions, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 55-18)
  - Agreement with CWU and APU, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 55-19)
  - Washington State Federation of Women's Clubs, 1949-1981 (Box-folder 56-1)
  - Employment Security, 1998- (Box-folder 56-2)
  - Bicycle Abuse on Campus, 2003- (Box-folder 56-3)
  - CWU Foundation Investment and Finance Committee, 2003- (Box-folder 56-4)
  - CWU Foundation Investment and Finance Committee, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 56-5)
  - Comprehensive Gift Campaign, 2005- (Box-folder 56-6)
  - Philanthropic Market Study Report, 2005- (Box-folder 56-7)
  - Asset Management, Roadmap, 2008- (Box-folder 56-8)
  - CWU Endowments, 2008-2010 (Box-folder 56-9)
  - Office of Management and Business, 2009- (Box-folder 56-10)
  - Continuing Education, Shared Revenue, 2010- (Box-folder 56-11)
  - Enterprise accounting Organization Chart, 2010- (Box-folder 56-12)
  - Property Transfers, 2010- (Box-folder 56-13)
  - Sale of Bonds, 2010-2014 (Box-folder 56-14)
  - Government University partner project, Efficiency and Effectiveness, 2011- (Box-folder 56-15)
  - 10 Year State Capital Plan, 2011- (Box-folder 56-16)
  - Center for Excellence and Leadership Agreement, 2011- (Box-folder 56-17)
  - Student Clubs, 2011- (Box-folder 56-18)
  - CWU Foundation Activities, 2012- (Box-folder 56-19)
  - CWU Federal Credit Union, Agreement, 2002-2011 (Box-folder 57-1)
  - CWU Research Foundation, 2002-2011 (Box-folder 57-2)
  - House Bill 1795, 2002-2011 (Box-folder 57-3)
  - CWU Bonds, 2002-2012 (Box-folder 57-4)
  - Early Childhood Learning Center, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 57-5)
  - IPEDS, Report, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 57-6)
  - Financial Report to Board of Trustees, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 57-7)
  - Grant Activities, 2011- (Box-folder 57-8)
  - Guanxi, China, Promotion, 2011- (Box-folder 57-9)
  - Organizational Effectiveness, 2011- (Box-folder 57-10)
  - Office of Program Research, 2011- (Box-folder 57-11)
  - Property Acquisitions, 2011- (Box-folder 57-12)
  - Conference Program, Goals and Metrics, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 57-13)
  - Debt Policy Report, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 57-14)
  - Community Economic Revitalization Board, 2012- (Box-folder 57-15)
  - Hogue Technology Building Addition Opening, 2012- (Box-folder 57-16)
  - Service and Activities Fees, Dispute, 2012- (Box-folder 57-17)
  - Emergency Plan, 2012- (Box-folder 57-18)
  - Information Services, Assessment, 2012-2013 (Box-folder 57-19)
  - ICAT,Committee, 2013- (Box-folder 57-20)
  - International Programs, 2013- (Box-folder 57-21)
  - Institute for Innovation and Entrepreneurship Advisory Group, 2013- (Box-folder 57-22)
  - Policies and Procedures Updates, 2004-2010 (Box-folder 58-1)
  - Payroll, Cost of Checks, Payment to Non-Resident, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 58-2)
  - Investments, Eligibility, Accounts, 2008-2011 (Box-folder 58-3)
  - Internal Audit, 2009- (Box-folder 58-4)
  - Kittitas County Strategic Plan, 2009- (Box-folder 58-5)
  - NACUBO Farm, 2009- (Box-folder 58-6)
  - CWU Foundation, Audit, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 58-7)
  - Bonds, Calculation Agency, 2010- (Box-folder 58-8)
  - Calculation Collection Agency, Bond Agreement, Statement of Revenue, 2010- (Box-folder 58-9)
  - CWU Bonds, Barclay, 2010- (Box-folder 58-10)
  - Legislative Reporting, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 58-11)
  - Moody's Public University Disclosure, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 58-12)
  - Office of Financial Management, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 58-13)
  - KCWU, Policies, 2011- (Box-folder 58-14)
  - Construction Notification, 1998-2013 (Box-folder 59-1)
  - Budget Cut Scenarios, 2010- (Box-folder 59-2)
  - Board of Trustees, 2011- (Box-folder 59-3)
  - Services and Activities, 2011- (Box-folder 59-4)
  - Board of Trustees, 2012- (Box-folder 59-5)
  - Board of Trustees, 2012- (Box-folder 59-6)
  - Board of Trustees, 2012- (Box-folder 59-7)
  - Board of Trustees, 2012- (Box-folder 59-8)
  - Board of Trustees, 2012- (Box-folder 59-9)
  - Board of Trustees, 2013- (Box-folder 59-10)
  - Board of Trustees, 2013- (Box-folder 59-11)
  - Board of Trustees, 2013- (Box-folder 59-12)
  - Board of Trustees, 2013- (Box-folder 59-13)
  - Board of Trustees, 2013- (Box-folder 59-14)
  - Board of Trustees, 2013- (Box-folder 59-15)
  - Board of Trustees, 2014- (Box-folder 59-16)
  - Board of Trustees, 2014- (Box-folder 59-17)
  - Board of Trustees, 2014- (Box-folder 59-18)
  - Business Affairs Council, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 60-1)
  - CWU Commercial Activities, 2004-2012 (Box-folder 60-2)
  - Business Affairs Council, 2005- (Box-folder 60-3)
  - Budget Memo, 2009- (Box-folder 60-4)
  - Capital Budget, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 60-5)
  - Boiler Stack Recovery, 2012- (Box-folder 60-6)
  - Enrollment Management, Organizational Chart, 2012- (Box-folder 60-7)
  - South Neighborhood, 2012- (Box-folder 60-8)
  - FMD Agenda, 2013- (Box-folder 60-9)
  - Employee Council, Overview, 2013- (Box-folder 60-10)
  - Hobson's Strategic Enrollment Partnership Program, 2013- (Box-folder 60-11)
  - Capital Budget, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 61-1)
  - Capital Budget Hearing, 1992- (Box-folder 61-2)
  - Budget Hearings, Summary, 1995- (Box-folder 61-3)
  - Capital Policy Committee, 1996- (Box-folder 61-4)
  - Budget Hearings, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 61-5)
  - Capital Budgets Requests, 2001-2005 (Box-folder 61-6)
  - Strategic Plan, Goals, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 61-7)
  - Ventrees, Bill Reader File, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 61-8)
  - Council of Presidents, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 61-9)
  - Business and Financial Services, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 61-10)
  - Information Technology Services, 2006- (Box-folder 61-11)
  - Auxiliaries, 2007- (Box-folder 61-12)
  - Business Affairs Council, 2007- (Box-folder 61-13)
  - Human Resources, 2007- (Box-folder 61-14)
  - President's Cabinet, 2007- (Box-folder 61-15)
  - Auditor's Entrance Office, 2007- (Box-folder 61-16)
  - Capital Projects Evaluation, Reports, 2008- (Box-folder 61-17)
  - Communications Team, 1997- (Box-folder 62-1)
  - Maintenance of Nonacademic Building, 1999- (Box-folder 62-2)
  - Ad Hoc Dispute Resolution Committee, 2001- (Box-folder 62-3)
  - Development Oversight Committee, 2001- (Box-folder 62-4)
  - Development Priorities Committee, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 62-5)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, Minutes, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 62-6)
  - President's Advisory Council, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 62-7)
  - Alternative Energy, 2009- (Box-folder 62-8)
  - Kittitas County Solid Waste Committee, 2009- (Box-folder 62-9)
  - Tuition Rate, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 62-10)
  - Keys, Floor Plans, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 62-11)
  - Student Financial Services, Accounts Balances, 2011- (Box-folder 62-12)
  - Student Success, Dean Overview, 2011- (Box-folder 62-13)
  - Use of State Resources, 2011- (Box-folder 62-14)
  - Supplementary Budget, 2011- (Box-folder 62-15)
  - Economic Outlook Conference, 2011- (Box-folder 62-16)
  - Monthly Project and Expense Reports, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 62-17)
  - Seattle Office, 2012- (Box-folder 62-18)
  - Hogue Donor Signage, 2012- (Box-folder 62-19)
  - Spring Reception, 2012- (Box-folder 62-20)
  - Student Union Recreation Center Governance, 2012- (Box-folder 62-21)
  - Permanent Presidency, 2012- (Box-folder 62-22)
  - Facilities Maintenance, 2013- (Box-folder 62-23)
  - Business Plan Analysis, 2015- (Box-folder 62-24)
  - Higher Education Coordinating Board, 1991-2008 (Box-folder 63-1)
  - CWU and Foundation Agreement, 1995-2007 (Box-folder 63-2)
  - Budget Restructure, 2002-2008 (Box-folder 63-3)
  - Housing Budget, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 63-4)
  - Housing Dining, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 63-5)
  - Occupancy Report, 2006- (Box-folder 63-6)
  - Dining Services, 2006-2009 (Box-folder 63-7)
  - CWU Innovation Fund, 2006-2013 (Box-folder 63-8)
  - Memorandum of Understanding, Online Course Development, 2008- (Box-folder 63-9)
  - International Recruitment, 2009- (Box-folder 63-10)
  - Custodial Staff, Business Affairs Council, 2010- (Box-folder 63-11)
  - Fraternity and Sorority Life, Advisory Board, 2010- (Box-folder 63-12)
  - Higher Education Coordinating Board, 2010- (Box-folder 63-13)
  - Debt Peer Analysis, 2011- (Box-folder 63-14)
  - Dining Services Feasibility Analysis, 2012- (Box-folder 63-15)
  - Legislative Update, 2012- (Box-folder 63-16)
  - Board of Trustees Documents, 2012- (Box-folder 63-17)
  - Academic Planning Task Force, 2012-2013 (Box-folder 63-18)
  - Beginning Fund Balance, Requests, 2012-2013 (Box-folder 63-19)
  - Service and Fees Base Funding, 2014- (Box-folder 63-20)
  - Information Technology Services, Warehouse, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 64-1)
  - Background Check, 2009- (Box-folder 64-2)
  - Board of Trustees, Minutes, 2009- (Box-folder 64-3)
  - Business Affairs Council, 2009- (Box-folder 64-4)
  - CWU Transit, 2009- (Box-folder 64-5)
  - Data Project Charter, 2009- (Box-folder 64-6)
  - President Gaudino, An Inauguration Speech, 2009- (Box-folder 64-7)
  - President's Task Force on Retention, 2009- (Box-folder 64-8)
  - Evaluation Report, NWCCU, 2009- (Box-folder 64-9)
  - Expenditures, 2009- (Box-folder 64-10)
  - Provost, Academic Planning, 2009- (Box-folder 64-11)
  - University Center Planning, Historical Timeline, 2009- (Box-folder 64-12)
  - Correspondence, Water park, 2009- (Box-folder 64-13)
  - President's Advisory Council, Minutes, 2009-2013 (Box-folder 64-14)
  - Ground Squirrel Repellant, Trapping at CWU, 2009- (Box-folder 64-15)
  - University Enrollment Plan, 2009- (Box-folder 64-16)
  - Research Ethics, Conflicts of Interests, 2009- (Box-folder 64-17)
  - Travel Policies, 2009- (Box-folder 64-18)
  - President's Cabinet Meeting, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 64-19)
  - Bow Wave Funding Needs, Information Technology Needs, 2010- (Box-folder 64-20)
  - Catering Procedures, 2010- (Box-folder 64-21)
  - Credit Card Policies, 2010- (Box-folder 64-22)
  - Facility Condition Index, 2010- (Box-folder 64-23)
  - Fund 57, New Residence Funding, 2010- (Box-folder 64-24)
  - Hanover Research Reports, 2010- (Box-folder 64-25)
  - Spending Freeze, Office of Financial Management, 2010- (Box-folder 64-26)
  - Student Media Board Charter, Merger, 2010- (Box-folder 64-27)
  - Technology Transformation Task Force, 2010- (Box-folder 64-28)
  - Tuition and Fees Presentation, 2010- (Box-folder 64-29)
  - Excess Tuition, 2011- (Box-folder 64-30)
  - Grievances, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 65-1)
  - Custodial data, 2006- (Box-folder 65-2)
  - Corona, Rich Calendar, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 65-3)
  - Auxiliary Services, 2008- (Box-folder 65-4)
  - Business Affairs Council, 2008- (Box-folder 65-5)
  - Financial Holds, 2008- (Box-folder 65-6)
  - President's Advisory Council, 2008- (Box-folder 65-7)
  - Human Resources, 2008-2010 (Box-folder 65-8)
  - Budget Template, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 65-9)
  - Welcome Center, 2011- (Box-folder 65-10)
  - Budget Cuts, Recession, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 66-1)
  - Boundaryless Group, 2004- (Box-folder 66-2)
  - Boards of Trustees Agenda, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 66-3)
  - Enrollment Management and Financial Aid Taskforce Data, 2005-2011 (Box-folder 66-4)
  - Board of Trustees Agenda Items, 2006- (Box-folder 66-5)
  - Board of Trustees Agenda, 2008- (Box-folder 66-6)
  - CWU Foundation Statement, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 66-7)
  - Enrollment Task Force First Declared By Campus, 2010- (Box-folder 66-8)
  - Enrollment Management, Correspondence, 2011- (Box-folder 66-9)
  - Enrollment Management and Financial Aid Planning Taskforce, Agendas, 2011- (Box-folder 66-10)
  - Enrollment Management and Financial Aid Planning Taskforce, final draft, 2011- (Box-folder 66-11)
  - Enrollment Management and Financial Aid Taskforce ,Trends, 2011- (Box-folder 66-12)
  - International Recruitment Program, 2011- (Box-folder 66-13)
  - Year 2000, Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 67-1)
  - Phase 1 Program, Year 2000 Risk Assessment, 1999- (Box-folder 67-2)
  - Year 2000 Risk Assessment, Disclosure, 1999- (Box-folder 67-3)
  - Year 2000 Risk Assessment, Statewide Report, 1999- (Box-folder 67-4)
  - Year 2000 Risk Assessment Program Phase 3, 1999- (Box-folder 67-5)
  - Year 2000 Risk Assessment, Statewide Report, 1999- (Box-folder 67-6)
  - Year 2000 Risk Assessment, Statewide Report, 1999- (Box-folder 67-7)
  - Business Continuing Work Group, Year 2000, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 67-8)
  - Overall Year 2000 contingency Planning, NonIT Year 2000 Steering Committee, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 67-9)
  - Recruitment and Retention Report, 2005-2010 (Box-folder 67-10)
  - State Boosts to Budget, 2005- (Box-folder 68-1)
  - Dining Services Analysis, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 68-2)
  - Audit, Discussion, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 68-3)
  - Moody's Report, 2007- (Box-folder 68-4)
  - Statement of Net Assets, unaudited, 2007- (Box-folder 68-5)
  - Standing Committee's Annual Report, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 68-6)
  - University Department Organizational Charts, 2007- (Box-folder 68-7)
  - Enrollment Benchmarks, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 68-8)
  - Facilities, Work Orders, 2008- (Box-folder 68-9)
  - Internal Auditor, Review, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 68-10)
  - Budget Presentation to Board of Trustees, 2009- (Box-folder 68-11)
  - Human Resources Department, Reorganization, 2009- (Box-folder 68-12)
  - Human Resources Department, Strategic Plan, 2009- (Box-folder 68-13)
  - Identity Theft Prevention, 2009- (Box-folder 68-14)
  - Waivers, Work Study, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 68-15)
  - Assistant Vice President financial Services, Direct Reports Staff Meeting, 2011- (Box-folder 68-16)
  - Financial Aid Hold, Subcommittee, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 68-17)
  - Facilities Planning, Well Agreement, 2010- (Box-folder 68-18)
  - Budget Considerations, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 68-19)
  - Letter From College of the Sciences, Action Plan, 2011- (Box-folder 68-20)
  - Science Neighborhood, Board of Trustees Minutes, 2011- (Box-folder 68-21)
  - CWCE Business Office miscellaneous Accounts ledger, 1938-1942 (Box-folder 68-22)
  - Retirement and Insurance Committee, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 69-1)
  - Emergency Preparedness Plan, 1999-2007 (Box-folder 69-2)
  - Commercial Activities Committee, 1999-2009 (Box-folder 69-3)
  - President's Advisory Council, 2001- (Box-folder 69-4)
  - President's Cabinet, 2001- (Box-folder 69-5)
  - President's Cabinet, 2002- (Box-folder 69-6)
  - President's Advisory Committee, 2002- (Box-folder 69-7)
  - Equal Opportunity Grievance Committee, 2002-2008 (Box-folder 69-8)
  - Athletic Facility Title IX Compliance Building Committee, 2003- (Box-folder 69-9)
  - President's Cabinet, 2003- (Box-folder 69-10)
  - President's Cabinet, 2003- (Box-folder 69-11)
  - Diversity Committee, 2004- (Box-folder 69-12)
  - Classified Staff Grievance Committee, 2005- (Box-folder 69-13)
  - Board of Trustees, 2006- (Box-folder 69-14)
  - South Neighborhood Building, 2006- (Box-folder 69-15)
  - Parking Advisory Committee, 2006-2009 (Box-folder 69-16)
  - Development Priorities Committee, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 69-17)
  - Department Number Changes, 2008- (Box-folder 69-18)
  - VP Budget, 2008-2013 (Box-folder 69-19)
  - University Information Technology Advisory Committee, 2009- (Box-folder 69-20)
  - Spending Plan, 2010- (Box-folder 69-21)
  - Management Information Systems, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 69-22)
  - BIT Chartfield Training Tape One, PeopleSoft, Business Information (Box-folder 70-12)
  - Technology Presentation, Training to CWU at CWU Workshop (Box-folder 70-3)
  - BIT Chartfield Training Tape, PeopleSoft, Business Information (Box-folder 70-4)
  - BIT Chartfield Training Tape Three (Box-folder 70-5)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Abdul Nasser Presentation 12121997 (Box-folder 70-6)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting October 15, 1999 Tape 1 of 2 (Box-folder 70-7)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting October 15, 1999 Tape 2 of 2 (Box-folder 70-8)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Summer Session 2005 1-13-05 (Box-folder 70-9)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting March 7, 2000 (Box-folder 70-10)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting March 14, 2000 Tape 1 of2 (Box-folder 70-11)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting March 14, 2000 Tape 2 of2 (Box-folder 70-12)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting March 15, 2000 (Box-folder 70-13)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting March 17, 2000 (Box-folder 70-14)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting March 27, 2000 Tape 1 of 2 (Box-folder 70-15)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting March 27, 2000 Tape 1 of2 (Box-folder 70-16)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting March 27, 2000 Tape 2of2 (Box-folder 70-17)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting March 27, 2000 Tape 2of2 (Box-folder 70-18)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting March 30, 2000 (Box-folder 70-19)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting March 30, 2000 (Box-folder 70-20)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting April 24, 2003 Barge 412 (Box-folder 70-21)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting 6-4-2003 (Box-folder 70-22)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting 2-3-2004 (Box-folder 70-23)
  - Budget Advisory Committee Meeting 4-28-2004 (Box-folder 70-24)
  - Budget Advisory Committee 4/19/2002 (Box-folder 70-25)
  - Budget Advisory Committee 4/19/2002 (Box-folder 70-26)
  - Budget Advisory Committee 4-12-06, 2006- (Box-folder 70-27)
  - Budget Advisory 1-24-03, 2003- (Box-folder 70-28)
  - Budget Advisory Tele-Conference, 2002- (Box-folder 70-29)
  - Budget Hearing March 10,2000 (Box-folder 70-30)
  - Budget Hearing, 2001- (Box-folder 70-31)
  - Budget Meeting, 2005- (Box-folder 70-32)
  - Business and Financial Affairs "Solution Teams" Part 1, 1997- (Box-folder 70-33)
  - Business and Financial Affairs "Solution Teams" Part 2, 1997- (Box-folder 70-34)
  - Emergency Planning Workshop, 1999- (Box-folder 70-35)
  - Faculty Senate Meeting with presentation by Abdul Nasser., 1999- (Box-folder 70-36)
  - PeopleSoft Higher Education Customer Comments, 2000- (Box-folder 70-37)
  - Power Pole Presentation VERIII (Box-folder 70-38)
  - Strategic Planning Forum Abdul Nass4"er, 1997- (Box-folder 70-39)
  - Spring Budget Meeting, 2006- (Box-folder 70-40)
  - Yakima News Stories KNDO, 1999- (Box-folder 70-41)
  - Yakima News Stories (Box-folder 70-42)
  - Department Organization Charts, 1994-2013 (Box-folder 71-1)
  - Budgets and Reports, 1972-2012 (Box-folder 71-2)
  - Campus construction, Maps, 1999-2011 (Box-folder 71-3)
  - Ephemera, Newspaper Clippings, 1994-2009 (Box-folder 71-4)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, Summer Session, 2009- (Box-folder 72-12)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, Summer Session, 2008- (Box-folder 72-3)
  - College of Business Dean Search Committee, Canidate Interview, 2011- (Box-folder 72-4)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, Summer Session, 2006- (Box-folder 72-5)
  - Budget Meeting, 2005- (Box-folder 72-6)
  - Business Affairs Council Meeting, 1999- (Box-folder 72-7)
  - Budget Meeting, 2004- (Box-folder 72-8)
  - Summer Budget Presentation (Box-folder 72-9)
  - Budget Advisory Meeting, 2003- (Box-folder 72-10)
  - Greg Kummer (Box-folder 72-11)
  - PowerPoint Presentation (Box-folder 72-12)
  - PowerPoint Presentation (Box-folder 72-13)
  - Corona, Rich Archive 2 (Box-folder 72-14)
  - 5-May-05 (Box-folder 72-15)
  - Corona, Rich Archive 1 (Box-folder 72-16)
  - Archive disc 1, 2009- (Box-folder 72-17)
  - Archives, 2008- (Box-folder 72-18)
  - Budget Advisory, 2009- (Box-folder 72-19)
  - My Documents, Backup, 2008- (Box-folder 72-20)
  - Archive disc 2, 2009- (Box-folder 72-21)
  - Garden (Box-folder 72-22)
  - Budget Advisory Committee 4-16-08, 2008- (Box-folder 72-23)
  - Budget, 2008- (Box-folder 72-24)
  - Budget meeting, 2009- (Box-folder 72-25)
  - Board of Trustees archives, Operating Budget, Legislative Files, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 72-26)
  - Budget Information, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 72-27)
  - Commercial Activities of CWU, 1995-2013 (Box-folder 73-1)
  - Business Affairs Council, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 73-2)
  - Connie Williams, 2012-2014 (Box-folder 73-3)
  - Project Space Proposal, 2012- (Box-folder 73-4)
  - Tuition Model, 2014- (Box-folder 73-5)
  - Business Affairs Council Meeting Agendas, 2012-2013 (Box-folder 73-6)
  - Budget and Finance Committee: End of Year Report, 2012-2013 (Box-folder 73-7)
  - Business Affairs Council Meeting Agendas, 2013- (Box-folder 73-8)
  - President's Budget/Action Items, 2012-2014 (Box-folder 73-9)
  - Provost/VP BFA Correspondence Agendas, 2012-2014 (Box-folder 73-10)
  - Budget and Finance Committee, 2013-2014 (Box-folder 73-11)
  - BMilwaukee Railroad Abandonment, Newspapers Articles and Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 74-1)
  - Milwaukee Railroad Abandonment, Reports, 1979 (Box-folder 74-2)
  - Milwaukee Railroad Abandonment, Reports, 1979 (Box-folder 74-3)
  - Milwaukee Railroad Abandonment, Blueprints, Correspondence, and Newspapers Articles, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 74-4)
  - Milwaukee Railroad Abandonment, Interstate Commerce Commission Decision and Report, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 74-5)
  - Auxiliary Services Business Plan, 2012-2016 (Box-folder 75-1)
  - Commercial Activities, 2012- (Box-folder 75-2)
  - Continuing Education Business Plan, 2011- (Box-folder 75-3)
  - Facilities Master Plan, 2011- (Box-folder 75-4)
  - JLARC Study, 2010- (Box-folder 75-5)
  - Operating Budget Subcommittee, 2010- (Box-folder 75-6)
  - Sports and Event Center Strategic Plan, 2010- (Box-folder 75-7)
  - University Standing Committees, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 75-8)